http://www.traviswolff.com/privacy-policy/

Trends & Insights
Offering our expertise, guidance and thought leadership on trends and insights that affect organizations. This section delivers articles and thought leadership pieces to help simplify the complexities businesses face in an ever expanding and changing environment.
Trending Today
Furlough FAQ – What Employers Need to Consider
A staff furlough might be a more strategic option than a lay-off.
LEARN MORE »
COVID-19 State Relief Matrix
Relief opportunities are changing daily, our SALT specialists have summarized these opportunities.
LEARN MORE »
CARES Act: Higher Education Relief Fund
Funds must be used to provide students with financial aid.
LEARN MORE »
People
SpotLight
Matt Armanino
As chief executive officer and managing partner, Matt focuses on firm-wide growth and bringing innovation to every part of the firm’s infrastructure in order to better create value and drive successful outcomes for clients. He leads the development of Armanino’s short- and long-term plans, including strategic partnerships, new solutions...
READ MORE »
Search People By Function OR
Alphabetical by Last Name
A
B
C
D
E
F
Offices
BellevueDallasDenverDowntown Los AngelesEl SegundoIrvineNapervilleSan FranciscoSan JoseSan RamonWest Los AngelesWoodland Hills
Departments
AuditBlockchainBusiness ManagementConsultingOf CounselOperationsRisk Assurance & Advisory ServicesTax
Services
Services
Audit
A-133 AuditAudit ProceduresBenefit Plan AuditsFinancial Statement AuditReviews & CompilationsSEC Audits
Risk Assurance & Advisory
Contract Compliance AuditsCybersecurity ServicesPrivacy ServicesHITRUSTInternal AuditISO 27001SOC AuditSOX ComplianceThird-Party Assurance
Tax
Corporate Tax OutsourcingFederal Tax PreparationIPO Tax ConsultingTax Credits & IncentivesSales and Use TaxState and Local TaxTax ProvisionIndividual Tax PlanningInternational Tax ServicesTransfer PricingNonprofit Tax Services
Private Wealth
Family Office ServicesIndividual Tax PlanningTrust & Estate Planning
Blockchain
Business Management
Consulting
Artificial Intelligence LabBusiness Application ConsultingBusiness Application StrategyBusiness IntelligenceCustomer Relationship Management (CRM)Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP)Financial Planning & Analysis ServicesManaged ServicesBusiness Outsourcing ServicesCorporate FinanceExecutive SearchHR OutsourcingFinance and Accounting ServicesInterim Financial ManagementRestructuring Services
CFO Consulting & AdvisoryBusiness ValuationsCompensation & Benefits PlanningEquity Management ConsultingForensic AccountingIPO ReadinessLease Accounting (ASC 842) Mergers & Acquisitions (M&A)Revenue Recognition (ASC 606)Technical AccountingCloud SolutionsStrategy and TransformationSystems Implementation
Software Solutions
Software Solutions
Step-by-Step Guide to Selecting an ERP Solution
An ERP solution is an important investment but the selection process can be a daunting task. Our straightforward guide provides a comprehensive framework of considerations to drive your selection process.
Get Your Free ERP Selection Guide
Software Products
BlackLineCertentMicrosoft DynamicsDynamics 365 BCDynamics 365 CRMDynamics 365 F&ODynamics GPDynamics UpgradesMicrosoft Power BISage IntacctSalesforceShareworksSolverWorkday Adaptive PlanningWorkiva
Integration Solutions
Software Integrations & Toolkits
Industries
Industries
Armanino is comprised of seasoned professionals who offer you a wealth of experience and insights across a broad range of industries and services. We work interactively and proactively to ensure our clients achieve their financial goals long-term.
Cannabis Consumer Business Cryptocurrency Education Higher EducationPrivate SchoolsEnergy Entertainment Financial Services Mortgage PoolsPrivate Equity FundsFood & Beverage
Franchise Healthcare Insurance Law Firms Life Sciences Medical DevicesPharmaceuticalsManufacturing, Distribution & Wholesale High-Tech
Nonprofit Professional Services Real Estate Solid Waste Technology SemiconductorSoftware & SaaS Companies
Events
Armanino offers webinars and live events to keep you informed and educated on business practices, processes, changes in rules and the latest trends and issues that affect your organization. Attending webinars and seminars are an effective method to gain knowledge on important issues from industry subject experts.
Search Events By
By Event TypeLive EventWebinarLocationMidwestNorthern CaliforniaPacific NorthwestSouthern California
Upcoming Events
10/15/20
Nonprofit State of the Industry Update Webinar
Register »
10/19/20
Armanino VIP Advantage Grand Ole Opry Virtual “Behind the Scenes” Tour
Register »
FIND MORE UPCOMING EVENTS »
Home > Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Armanino LLP (“Armanino”) provides this website privacy policy (the “Policy”) to provide information about our personal information handling practices for our website. It does not apply to personal information collected or provided offline.
If you choose to register or submit personally identifiable information to us through our website, such information will be processed in accordance with this Policy.
Types of Information Collected
Registration is not required for you to use our website. If you are merely a visitor, we only collect limited personal information through the use of cookies, which are described below. Personal information collected or provided will be processed and transferred by Armanino as described in this Policy.
If you submit any personal information applying for a job or internship, such personal information will be used, processed, transferred, and stored by Armanino for the purposes of recruitment and evaluations of qualifications for possible employment or internship possibilities. If selected for a position or internship, such personal information may also be used for onboarding activities.
You may choose to provide us with certain personal information when you contact us to subscribe to Armanino newsletters, register for events, and request information about Armanino services. The types of information that you may provide during your visit to the website may include:
name, title, company information, email address, telephone and fax number, and address.
You will know which personal information you have provided because you will have provided it yourself. By providing such information, you explicitly consent that Armanino may collect, use, process, store, and transfer such data to make contacts with you by telephone, email, or ground mail, to provide you with information and advertisements about Armanino and our services, to establish and maintain a customer or prospective customer relationship, and to evaluate, develop, and improve our services.
Should you subsequently choose to unsubscribe from mailing lists or any registrations, we will provide instructions within the appropriate website area or in communications to you and you may unsubscribe from subsequent email communications and registrations.
You can access California Consumer Privacy Act Disclosures by clicking here.
We have implemented reCAPTCHA v3 on our website and your use of reCAPTCHA is subject to the Google Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.
Cookies and Other Similar Technologies
On certain parts of the site, we may use cookies. “Cookies” are small text files stored in your browser that assist us in providing a more customized web experience. Cookies also allow us to understand site usage and improve the content and offerings on the site. We also may use cookies to offer you products or services. These cookies are not used to collect any personally identifiable information. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookies. If you are concerned about cookies, most browsers permit users to decline cookies. If you reject cookies, you may still use the site; however, you may not be able to access all areas or features.
Most web browsers include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected.
No uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online.
Disclosure of Your Information
To the extent permitted by law, certain information about you may be disclosed in the following situations:
To comply with a validly issued and enforceable subpoena or summons.
To investigate network abuse.
As a part of any actual or threatened legal proceedings or alternative dispute resolution proceedings either initiated by or against us.
To provide information to affiliates of the firm and nonaffiliated third parties who perform services or functions for us in conjunction with any requests or inquiries made by you.
For purposes of a business deal (or negotiation of a business deal) involving sale or transfer of all of part of our business or assets.
In an emergency, including to protect the safety of our employees or any person.
In connection with investigating and preventing fraud.
With your consent.
Security of Data
You should note that no transfer of data over the Internet is completely secure. While we use commercially-reasonable efforts to protect your data on our systems, when the data is transferred over the Internet, it may be accessed and used by unauthorized third parties. Armanino has no control over the performance, reliability, availability or security of the Internet and does not warrant that any information transfer via the Internet or any communication through the Internet is secure. Armanino shall not be liable for any disclosure, unauthorized use, loss, damage, expense, harm or inconvenience resulting from the loss, delay, interception, corruption, intervention, misuse or alteration of any personal data due to any reason beyond Armanino’s reasonable control.
Changes to the Policy and Contacts
From time to time we may revise our Policy. Any changes to this Policy will be posted on this website.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding your privacy while visiting our Website, please contact us at info@armaninollp.com or 12657 Alcosta Blvd, Suite 500, San Ramon, CA 94583, or at (925) 790-2600.
(Last Updated: March 9, 2020)
Why Armanino?
Business Stages
CFO Evolution
Corporate Responsibility
Recognition and Awards
Want To Grow?
IPO Readiness
Cloud Solutions
Geographic Expansion
Reporting & Analytics
SEC
Want To Talk?
Call us at 844-582-8883
Not a big talker? Email us at info@armaninoLLP.com
Want to Work Here?
We are always looking for talented people to join our firm. Apply now and become a part of our unique culture.
Stay in Touch
Sign up for Alerts, Education and Updates.
Register
Armanino is one of the top 25 largest independent accounting and business consulting firms in the United States. Armanino provides an integrated set of audit, tax, consulting, business management and technology solutions to companies in the U.S. and globally. The more global your company, the more value we can add to your organization.
In addition to its core consulting and accounting practices, Armanino operates its division—AMF Media Group (amfmediagroup.com), media and communications services and its affiliate and Intersect Capital (intersectcapitalllc.com), an independent financial planning, wealth and lifestyle management firm.
armanino llp
privacy policy
legal disclaimer
Copyright © Armanino LLP. All Rights Reserved.
